It is time for us to go picky picky for the record with actor, writer, comedian,
felonious monk. So you talk about having spent time in the incarceration system.
What is a song that reminds you of the day you got out?
I'm going to say One Love.
One Love from...
By Nas.
One Love. One Love. One Love.
A friend of mine, Harold Poole, wrote the lyrics to that song out in a letter that he wrote
me while I was locked up. For somebody to care about me enough to write down the lyrics
when we didn't have Genius. You know what I mean? Shout out to Rod. We didn't have Genius.
We didn't have lyrics for music lyric, that AZ lyric. We didn't have any of that. He had
to listen to the song over and over again. And Nas had a different flow. He had to write
and he wrote the whole song out line for line. And he saved my life from 92 to 98 multiple
times because I got a chance, well at least from 93, to read that letter over and over
again. And that song reminds me of coming home because somebody loved me that much.
Somebody cared about me that much. So yeah, that song.
We are, we are, we are.